# Ignacio Salvador Fidalgo

## **Aeronautical Engineer**

Tower road 69-73. Newquay TR7 1LX Telephone: 07876062124 e-mail: ji.sfidalgo@gmail.com Date of Birth: 08/03/1986

ID Card: 53621876-k

#### **PROFILE**

I am friendly person with good customer service skills gained throughout my previous work and experience. I am practical and always like to help people where I can, be organized and take a pride in what I do. One of my key strengths is my attention to detail and making sure that a task is completed to the highest of standards. Time keeping is important to me and I have always been very reliable and trusted by work colleagues and friends.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Customer service.
- Effective team member.
- Aware of Health and Safety.
- Tactfully problem solving.
- Punctual and reliable.
- IT Software including Microsoft Office, AUTOCAD, TRICALC.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2013. Traineeship in auditing at IPLUSF consultants.

- Research and development and implementation. Identifying, evaluating and focussing on airport projects.
- Dealing with clients and follow-up.
- Project technical and economic reports.
- In charge of supervising official and legal paperwork for funding.
- Licensing from local government: technical requirements and amendments.

#### **OTHER SECTORS**

- 2007-2011 Restaurants.
- 2010-2013 Waiter and events organiser at Samarkanda Catering.
- 2008-2012 Private teacher (Maths and Physics).
- 2011-12 Football trainer.
- 2009-2012 Football Team delegate (3<sup>rd</sup> division).

\_

## **EDUCATION**

2013. Aeronautical Engineer graduate at Universidad Politecnica Madrid. Specialising in airports. Project: Functionality of Alicante airport.

Technician's knowledge of tests in flight has presented me to the exam ,INTA in January 2014.

Studying course of adjustment to the Degree in Aerospace Engineering distantly. Presentation of the project June, 2014.

### **LANGUAGES**

• English: High level written and spoken level.

French: basic level.Spanish: native

## **OTHER INFORMATION**

- Flexibility.
- I am used to working in a team and a good communicator
- Initiative, analytical capacity.
- Right now Living in England.
- Availability completes to travel.
- Playing sports.

### **REFERENCE**

Reference are available.